stayonsearchcourse.com 2012-12-13

# Privacy Policy | StayOnSearch

**Last Updated: July 21, 2010**

StayOnSearch.com strives to offer its visitors the many advantages of Internet technology and to provide an interactive and personalized experience. We may use Personally Identifiable Information (your name, e-mail address, street address, telephone number) subject to the terms of this privacy policy. We will never sell, barter, or rent your email address to any unauthorized third party. Period.”

**How we gather information from users**

How we collect and store information depends on the page you are visiting, the activities in which you elect to participate and the services provided. For example, you may be asked to provide information when you register for access to certain portions of our site or request certain features, such as newsletters or when you make a purchase. You may provide information when you participate in sweepstakes and contests, message boards and chat rooms, and other interactive areas of our site. Like most Web sites, StayOnSearch.com also collects information automatically and through the use of electronic tools that may be transparent to our visitors. For example, we may log the name of your Internet Service Provider or use cookie technology to recognize you and hold information from your visit. Among other things, the cookie may store your user name and password, sparing you from having to re-enter that information each time you visit, or may control the number of times you encounter a particular advertisement while visiting our site. As we adopt additional technology, we may also gather information through other means. In certain cases, you can choose not to provide us with information, for example by setting your browser to refuse to accept cookies, but if you do you may be unable to access certain portions of the site or may be asked to re-enter your user name and password, and we may not be able to customize the site’s features according to your preferences.

**What we do with the information we collect**

Like other Web publishers, we collect information to enhance your visit and deliver more individualized content and advertising. We respect your privacy and do not share your information with anyone.

Aggregated Information (information that does not personally identify you) may be used in many ways. For example, we may combine information about your usage patterns with similar information obtained from other users to help enhance our site and services (e.g., to learn which pages are visited most or what features are most attractive). Aggregated Information may occasionally be shared with our advertisers and business partners. Again, this information does not include any Personally Identifiable Information about you or allow anyone to identify you individually.

We may use Personally Identifiable Information collected on StayOnSearch.com to communicate with you about your registration and customization preferences; our Terms of Service and privacy policy; services and products offered by StayOnSearch.com and other topics we think you might find of interest.  Personally Identifiable Information collected by StayOnSearch.com may also be used for other purposes, including but not limited to site administration, troubleshooting, processing of ecommerce transactions, administration of sweepstakes and contests, and other communications with you. Certain third parties who provide technical support for the operation of our site (our Web hosting service for example) may access such information. We will use your information only as permitted by law. In addition, from time to time as we continue to develop our business, we may sell, buy, merge or partner with other companies or businesses. In such transactions, user information may be among the transferred assets. We may also disclose your information in response to a court order, at other times when we believe we are reasonably required to do so by law, in connection with the collection of amounts you may owe to us, and/or to law enforcement authorities whenever we deem it appropriate or necessary.  Please note we may not provide you with notice prior to disclosure in such cases.

**Affiliated sites, linked sites and advertisements**

StayOnSearch.com expects its partners, advertisers and affiliates to respect the privacy of our users. Be aware, however, that third parties, including our partners, advertisers, affiliates and other content providers accessible through our site, may have their own privacy and data collection policies and practices.  For example, during your visit to our site you may link to, or view as part of a frame on a StayOnSearch.com page, certain content that is actually created or hosted by a third party. Also, through StayOnSearch.com you may be introduced to, or be able to access, information, Web sites, features, contests or sweepstakes offered by other parties. StayOnSearch.com is not responsible for the actions or policies of such third parties. You should check the applicable privacy policies of those third parties when providing information on a feature or page operated by a third party.

While on our site, our advertisers, promotional partners or other third parties may use cookies or other technology to attempt to identify some of your preferences or retrieve information about you. For example, some of our advertising is served by third parties and may include cookies that enable the advertiser to determine whether you have seen a particular advertisement before. Other features available on our site may offer services operated by third parties and may use cookies or other technology to gather information. StayOnSearch.com does not control the use of this technology by third parties or the resulting information, and is not responsible for any actions or policies of such third parties. You should also be aware that if you voluntarily disclose Personally Identifiable Information on message boards or in chat areas, that information can be viewed publicly and can be collected and used by third parties without our knowledge and may result in unsolicited messages from other individuals or third parties.  Such activities are beyond the control of StayOnSearch.com and this policy.

**Children**

StayOnSearch.com does not knowingly collect or solicit Personally Identifiable Information from or about children under 13 except as permitted by law. If we discover we have received any information from a child under 13 in violation of this policy, we will delete that information immediately. If you believe StayOnSearch.com has any information from or about anyone under 13, please contact us at the address listed below.

**Contacting Us**

We can be reached by contacting:

StayOnSearch.com  
Email: info(at)StayOnSearch.com

**Changes to this Policy**

StayOnSearch.com reserves the right to change this policy at any time. Please check this page periodically for changes. Your continued use of our site following the posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept those changes. Information collected prior to the time any change is posted will be used according to the rules and laws that applied at the time the information was collected.

**Governing law**

This policy and the use of this Site are governed by North Carolina law. If a dispute arises under this Policy we agree to first try to resolve it with the help of a mutually agreed-upon mediator in the following location: North Carolina. Any costs and fees other than attorney fees associated with the mediation will be shared equally by each of us. If it proves impossible to arrive at a mutually satisfactory solution through  
mediation, we agree to submit the dispute to binding arbitration at the following location: North Carolina, under the rules of the American Arbitration Association.  Judgment upon the award rendered by the arbitration may be entered in any court with jurisdiction to do so. StayOnSearch.com is controlled, operated and administered entirely within North Carolina. This statement and the policies outlined  
herein are not intended to and do not create any contractual or other legal rights in or on behalf of any party.

**External Links on StayOnSearch**

StayOnSearch links to other, external web sites that provide information we determine at our discretion contain the most useful information for our program.  While many sites provide very useful information, StayOnSearch only links to those sites which provide the most useful content. These links may be changed at any time as more useful sites come to our attention. The sole purpose of any external link is to enrich this site for our customers. All requests for inclusion of a link on this site is first and primarily evaluated with the needs of our customers in mind. Generally, external web sites do not meet the purposes of StayOnSearch if they contain, suggest, or infer any of the following:

1\. Advocacy of or opposition to any politically, environmentally, or socially controversial subjects, issues, or candidates.  
2\. Disparaging or promoting any person or class of persons.  
3\. External content not suitable for readers or viewers of all ages, or links to or other promotion of businesses whose products or services are not suitable for persons of all ages.  
4\. Promoting or inciting illegal, violent, or socially undesirable conduct.  
5\. Promotion or availability of alcohol or tobacco products.  
6\. Promotion or availability of illegal drugs.  
7\. Promotion or availability of adult or sexually oriented entertainment or materials.  
8\. Promotion, opposition, or availability of weapons.  
9\. Promotion, opposition, or availability of gambling.  
10\. Claims of efficacy, suitability, desirability, or other non-objective statements StayOnSearch © 2010 about businesses, products, or services.  
11\. Content that infringes on any trademark, copyright, or patent rights of another.  
12\. Claims or representations in violation of advertising or consumer protection laws.  
13\. Content that a reasonable citizen may not consider to maintain the dignity and decorum appropriate for government.

This list is a nonexclusive list. The external link policy applies only to web sites outside StayOnSearch. The webmaster shall establish procedures to monitor the implementation and continuing oversight of this policy. These procedures shall include a process for review of all new requests for external content links from StayOnSearch Web page to another page to ensure compliance with this policy prior to granting the request.

Each request for such a link shall be evaluated using the following guidelines: Is the content relevant?

Does the site provide information or services, which are not already available or linked to on StayOnSearch? If not, is the quality of the site comparable to or better than what is already provided?

Is the site well designed, easy to use, cross-browser compliant, and accessible to people with disabilities?

StayOnSearch reserves the right, at its sole discretion and without explanation, to withdraw at any time any external content for any reason.

**StayOnSearch Anti-Spam Policy**

This statement applies to StayOnSearch websites and services that display or link to this notice (“Services”). StayOnSearch prohibits the use of the Services in any manner associated with the transmission, distribution or delivery of any unsolicited bulk or unsolicited commercial e-mail (“Spam”). You may not use any Services to send Spam. You also may not deliver Spam or cause Spam to be delivered to any of StayOnSearch’s Services or customers.

In addition, e-mail sent, or caused to be sent, to or through the Services may not:

1\. Use or contain invalid or forged headers;  
2\. Use or contain invalid or non-existent domain names;  
3\. Employ any technique to otherwise misrepresent, hide or obscure any information in identifying the point of origin or the transmission path;  
4\. Use other means of deceptive addressing;  
5\. Use a third party’s internet domain name, or be relayed from or through a third party’s equipment, without permission of the third party;  
6\. Contain false or misleading information in the subject line or otherwise contain false or misleading content;  
7\. Fail to comply with additional technical standards described below; or  
8\. Otherwise violate the applicable Terms of Use for the Services.

StayOnSearch does not authorize the harvesting, mining or collection of e-mail addresses or other information from or through the Services. StayOnSearch does not permit or authorize others to use the Services to collect, compile or obtain any information about StayOnSearch’s customers or subscribers, including but not limited to subscriber e-mail addresses, which are StayOnSearchy’s confidential and  
StayOnSearch © 2010 proprietary information. Use of the Services is also subject to the applicable Privacy Statement and Terms of Use.

StayOnSearch does not permit or authorize any attempt to use the Services in a manner that could damage, disable, overburden or impair any aspect of any of the Services, or that could interfere with any other party’s use and enjoyment of any Service. If StayOnSearch believes that unauthorized or improper use is being made of any Service, it may, without notice, take such action as it, in its sole discretion, deems appropriate, including blocking messages from a particular internet domain, mail server or IP address.  StayOnSearch may immediately terminate any account on any Service, which it determines, in its sole discretion, is transmitting or is otherwise connected with any e-mail that violates this policy.  Nothing in this policy is intended to grant any right to transmit or send e-mail to, or through, the Services. Failure to enforce this policy in every instance does not amount to a waiver of StayOnSearch’s rights.  Unauthorized use of the Services in connection with the transmission of unsolicited e-mail, including the transmission of e-mail in violation of this policy, may result in civil, criminal, or administrative penalties against the sender and those assisting the sender.

**E-mail Privacy Policy**

We have created this email privacy policy to demonstrate our firm commitment to your privacy and the protection of your information.

**Why did you receive an email from us?**

If you received a mailing from us, (a) your email address is either listed with us as someone who has expressly shared this address for the purpose of receiving information in the future (“opt-in”), or (b) you have registered or purchased or otherwise have an existing relationship with us. We respect your time and attention by controlling the frequency of our mailings.

**How we protect your privacy**

We use security measures to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of data used by our system.

**Sharing and Usage**

We will never share, sell, or rent individual personal information with anyone without your advance permission or unless ordered by a court of law. Information submitted to us is only available to employees managing this information for purposes of contacting you or sending you emails based on your request for information and to contracted service providers for purposes of providing services relating to our communications with you.

**How can you stop receiving email from us?**

StayOnSearch © 2010 Each email sent contains an easy, automated way for you to cease receiving email from us, or to change your expressed interests. If you wish to do this, simply follow the instructions at the end of any email.  If you have received unwanted, unsolicited emails sent via this system or purporting to be sent via this system, please forward a copy of that email with your comments to info@stayonsearch.com for review.

**DMCA Disclaimer**

StayOnSearch.com respects the intellectual property of others. If you believe that your work has been copied in a way that constitutes copyright infringement, please follow our Notice and Procedures for Making Claims of Copyright Infringement below.

Notice and Procedure for Making Claims of Copyright Infringement Pursuant to the Digital Millennium Copyright Act.  If you believe that you hold a claim of copyright infringement against StayOnSearch.com, submit notice of your claim to the following Designated Agent:

Service Provider: StayOnSearch.com

Email Address to Which Notification Should Be Sent:  
info@stayonsearch.com This e-mail address is being protected from spam bots, you need JavaScript enabled to view it.  To be effective, the notification of your claim of copyright infringement should be written and should include the following:

A statement that you are the owner of the exclusive right you claim has been infringed, or a statement that you are authorized to act on behalf of the owner of an exclusive right that has allegedly been infringed.  A statement, under penalty of perjury, that the information in the notification is accurate. Your signature. (The signature may be electronic.)  The identification of the copyrighted work you claim has been infringed. (If you StayOnSearch © 2010 claim that multiple copyrighted works have been infringed you can submit one notification with a list of the allegedly infringed works.)  Identification of the material that you claim to be infringing and information reasonably sufficient to permit StayOnSearch.com to locate the material.  Information reasonably sufficient to permit StayOnSearch.com to contact you, including your address, telephone number, fax number and, if available, an electronic mail address. You can provide contact information for the owner of the exclusive right that you claim has been infringed if you are not the owner, but rather authorized to act on behalf of the owner.  A statement you have a good-faith belief that use of the material in the manner complained of is not authorized by the copyright owner, its agent, or the law. StayOnSearch.com will respond to any DMCA complaints in a timely manner.  Should you be the copyright holder of a specific piece of content featured on this site without your permission, StayOnSearch.com will remove it in a timely manner once notified.

Copyright (c) 2010, StayOnSearch.com.  All Rights Reserved.
